https://www.bcbsal.org/web/privacy-statement

Benefit Summary
Account Summary   Claim Statements   Reimbursements   Contract and Dependent Information   Other Insurance Coverage   Deductible & Out of Pocket Costs   View Benefits and Coverage
Resources
Review and Pay my Bill   ID Cards   Forms and Materials   Covered ImmunizationsHealth Insurance BasicsPolicies and GuidelinesPreventive Services
Find a Doctor
Self Service
Find a DoctorSymptom CheckerTeladocTreatment Cost Estimator
Benefits
Access2Day Health Locations - Find the nearest location for rapid inpatient and outpatient careBlue Distinction Centers - Learn about healthcare facilities and providers recognized for their expertise in delivering specialty care
myHealth
Free Health Programs
Baby Yourself - free gifts and a personal nurse offer support for a healthy pregnancyTalk to a nurse or advisor - do you have questions about your health?Silver Sneakers - where seniors have free access to nearly 200 fitness centersCare Reminders   Blue365 - Discounts & deals on gym memberships, fitness gear, healthy eating options, & more.
myBlueWellness
Personal Health Record   Health Quiz (Health Quotient)   My Health Assistant   WebMD Home    EventsBe Healthy School DayNational Walk@Lunch Day
Pharmacy
Pharmacy Tools
Pharmacy ResourcesHome Delivery NetworkPrescription Drug ListsFind a Pharmacy
Prescription Resources
Frequently Asked QuestionsDrug Coverage GuidelinesFile a Drug Claim OnlinePrescription History
Shop Plans
Health Plans
Individual & FamilyEmployersMedicare (65+)Account-Based PlansFederal Employee Program (FEP)
Additional Plans
Health & Dental PlansVisionTravelDental
Contact Us
Feedback
Sign in to myBlueCross
New to myBlueCross? Register
GO
Remember Username
Forgot username or password?
SIGN IN
Individual
Medicare
Group
Provider
SIGN IN
About Us
Feedback
Contact Us
Search
X
myBlueCross
Benefit Summary
Account Summary Claim Statements Reimbursements Contract and Dependent Information Other Insurance Coverage Deductible & Out of Pocket Costs View Benefits and Coverage
Resources
Review and Pay my Bill ID Cards Forms and Materials Covered ImmunizationsHealth Insurance BasicsPolicies and GuidelinesPreventive Services
Find a Doctor
Self Service
Find a DoctorSymptom CheckerTeladocTreatment Cost Estimator
Benefits
Access2Day Health Locations - Find the nearest location for rapid inpatient and outpatient careBlue Distinction Centers - Learn about healthcare facilities and providers recognized for their expertise in delivering specialty care
myHealth
Free Health Programs
Baby Yourself - free gifts and a personal nurse offer support for a healthy pregnancyTalk to a nurse or advisor - do you have questions about your health?Silver Sneakers - where seniors have free access to nearly 200 fitness centersCare Reminders Blue365 - Discounts & deals on gym memberships, fitness gear, healthy eating options, & more.
myBlueWellness
Personal Health Record Health Quiz (Health Quotient) My Health Assistant WebMD Home  EventsBe Healthy School DayNational Walk@Lunch Day
Pharmacy
Pharmacy Tools
Pharmacy ResourcesHome Delivery NetworkPrescription Drug ListsFind a Pharmacy
Prescription Resources
Frequently Asked QuestionsDrug Coverage GuidelinesFile a Drug Claim OnlinePrescription History
Shop Plans
Health Plans
Individual & FamilyEmployersMedicare (65+)Account-Based PlansFederal Employee Program (FEP)
Additional Plans
Health & Dental PlansVisionTravelDental
Home >Privacy Statement
About Us
Contact Us
Careers
Fraud & Abuse
HIPAA Privacy Notice
Privacy Statement
Accessibility Information
Legal Disclaimer
Help
Web Content Display (Global)
Privacy Statement
Because we value your relationship with us, we have detailed below our privacy objectives for our Web site:
Security Practices
We recognize and respect your desire for privacy when it comes to your personal and health care affairs. We attempt to protect online information according to established company security standards and practices, and we continually evaluate new technologies for safeguarding information.
Use of Email
Please use your own best judgment when sending information via the Internet to an email address. Email sent via the Internet may pass through private and public networks with varying levels of security. Some networks may have taken steps to secure email transmissions while others have not, thereby compromising the privacy and integrity of an email. An email may be copied, altered or destroyed.
If you have personal or confidential information to relay to our company, please call the appropriate member service phone number that you will find in Contact Us.
We preserve the content of your email, your email address and our response so that we can efficiently respond to questions you might have. We also do this in an effort to meet legal and regulatory requirements.
We will respect your request to be, or not to be, contacted by email.
Cookies, Surveys and Forms
You may have the opportunity to provide information to us through online surveys and forms. We use this information to better understand health care needs and to provide quality products, services and other opportunities. We want your visit to our web site to be informative and enjoyable. We plan to use any information we obtain from you to help us continually improve the content, functionality and overall usefulness of our Web site; but in no way we will make specific and individually identifiable information given to us available without your specific consent.
As you browse, we may install cookies (tiny text files stored on your computer which record your preferences) in your browser. Cookies cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personally identifiable information. We may disclose this non-personally identifiable information to our staff and to trusted third parties involved in the marketing of our products and services. We do not sell or rent this non-personally identifiable information to third parties.
In addition to our use of first party cookies on our website, we allow certain Third Parties to include web beacons within our web pages. Web beacons are image requests which are used by the third party to install their own cookie in your browser. These companies are our vendors who have been hired for marketing or research purposes. Member identifiable data will not be transmitted. The use of these web beacons is subject to the privacy policies of these Third Parties, not our Privacy Policy. At an advertiser's discretion, Google Analytics data may be examined in concert with data about the advertiser's ads that have been shown using the Google Display Network or DoubleClick for Advertisers. Thus, an advertiser can understand how anonymous users interacted with the advertiser's website after seeing the advertiser's ads.
Advertisers may use this data to inform and optimize their ad campaigns.
Users may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of your use of Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.
Mobile Device Applications ("Apps")
Information that we receive through the use of any of our Apps, including, but not limited to, the number of times that you use the App and information that you submit, is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. When you download and install one of our Apps onto your mobile device, certain information may be saved to your device for certain App functionality enhancements. We do not obtain any information about your mobile device, other than the brand, make and model and type of operating software your device uses.
Our Apps obtain your consent (via an opt-in) before using information from pin-pointing technology like GPS or cell tower information. You can withdraw your consent (opt-out) for the use of "location" at any time by changing your location services in the "Settings" function on your mobile device.
Updates to the Statement
Evolving technology will continue to provide us with new and better ways to collect and use information so that we may better serve your health coverage needs. We may revise or update this Privacy Statement in the future to reflect these technological advances, and we encourage you to return to this page from time to time for any updates.
Confidentiality
Again, please use your own best judgment when sending information via the Internet to an email address.
If you have personal or confidential information to relay to our company and have concerns about the security of your email, please call the appropriate member service phone number that you will find in Contact Us. If you do provide personal information, such as an email, telephone or fax number, or other identifying information, we do not plan to disclose it without your consent. We maintain this information, as well as all web based transactions, according to our usual high, government regulated, security and confidentiality standards.
Company
About Us
Contact Us
Careers
Community Involvement
Newsroom
Other Websites
GroupAccess
©2020, Blue Cross Blue Shield of Alabama is an independent licensee of the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association.
